[rock guitar riff playing]
[Gwen, straining] Leia, take the picture.
My eyes are burning. I need to blink.
There's only 24 pictures on this camera,
and I don't want to waste any of them.
[shutter clicks]
Twenty-three.
I just took one of Ozzie's butt.
Send me a copy.
I can never get a good angle.
Why don't I take the pictures?
Oh great! Try to make me look really cool.
It's just a camera.
Ready to party?
I got the snacks. Nate's got the keg.
[loud clanging]
Sorry!
[panting]
I walked into a spiderweb,
and she got away from me.
Dude, it's Leia's last night,
and you brought that nasty keg
from Fourth of July?
I took care of this thing
like it's my baby.
Till I dropped it down the stairs.
Just like Mom did to you?
Burn!
Bro.
Old, flat, skunky beer?
We are not this desperate.
-["I Wish" plays]
-♪ I wish I was a little bit taller ♪
♪ I wish I was a baller ♪
♪ I wish I had a girl who looked good
I would call her ♪
♪ I wish I had a rabbit in a hat
With a bat ♪
-♪ And a six-four Impala ♪
-[shutter clicks]
♪ I wish I was like six-foot-nine
So I can get with Leoshi ♪
♪ 'Cause she don't know me
But yo, she's really fine ♪
♪ You know I see her all the time
Everywhere I go ♪
♪ And even in my dreams
I can scheme of ways to make her mine ♪
-♪ 'Cause I know she's livin' phat ♪
-[song ends]
I think I'm a really good dancer.
It's your last night, so… sure.
Ozzie, are you gonna be sad when I'm gone?
Uh…
No.
He isn't great
about expressing his emotions.
If I say how I feel,
people say how they feel.
And I don't care.
Well, this is the perfect last night
to cap off the perfect summer.
I'll drink to that.
[chuckles] Bro.
I was worried when you had that talk
with Leia about breaking things off,
it was gonna harsh the mood.
But it didn't!
I'm having a blast!
[chuckles]
I haven't told her yet.
What?
-[shutter clicks]
-[rock music plays]
One, two, three, four!
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
♪ We're all all right! ♪
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
-You're breaking up with me?
-No, no, no. Don't say it like that.
It's not a breakup.
It's like we were boyfriend
and girlfriend,
but we're gonna stop.
That's a breakup, you donk!
Oh my God, I'm one of
your summer things, you jerk.
Whoa. She cheesied your deezy.
Leia, I'm not being a jerk.
We're gonna be apart for nine months.
Long distance relationships are hard.
[chuckles] Hard.
I don't want to put us through that.
So that's it? We're not even gonna try?
Leia, I know you're upset,
but he's making a lot of sense.
This way you both can go off
and live your lives. Right, babe?
Yeah, long distance is nuts.
Nuts. [chuckles]
[Jay gulps]
It's not for the faint of heart.
Do you know how much it costs
to call my boyfriend in Canada?
Well, your grandparents
are about to find out.
Gwen, help me out here.
He has a point.
You're with them?
No, I'm looking out for you.
I mean, it is a long time apart, and also…
man-whore.
-Unbelievable!
-Leia…
Do not follow me!
I am not afraid to use this thing!
[rock music playing]
Hold on. Let me get her.
Leia, phone!
I thought you'd be in a worse mood,
what with Leia leaving.
I was upset, but then I realized
she won't be gone for long.
Her boyfriend is here,
her best friend lives next door,
and she loves my potato salad.
And what about me? I'm fun.
Hey, Grandma.
Hi, sweetie. It's Jay.
Oh.
-You suck!
-[phone dings]
Oh dear.
Hey, Leia. You feeling any better?
[phone ringing]
[loud clanging]
Oh, I just… I… I don't think she is.
Okay, so what's going on here?
Boyfriend stuff, me stuff,
and yesterday she got sick
from some weird potato salad.
Oh my God! Those are the big-ticket items!
She may not want to come back
next summer. I gotta talk to her.
Good luck.
Oh no.
Don't everyone leave.
Then it'll just be me and my newspaper.
[tree trunk cracking]
[loud thud]
Your tree could've killed someone.
I should sue.
My tree?
That tree came from your property.
Oh, then we'll call it an act of God.
Could've happened to the best of us.
But it didn't happen to the best of us.
It happened to you.
I have been telling you
that this tree is rotting,
and you need to take care of it.
I've been busy.
Doing what?
That would be me.
Oh, come on!
You had time to put on pants.
My pants take time to wiggle into.
Sometimes I have to, uh, grease my thighs.
This is attractive to you?
We bumped into each other at the Chili's,
and we decided to give it another try.
Yeah, it turned out I wanted…
♪ My baby back, baby back ♪
Could we get back to the tree?
You need to get ahold of your landlord
and get rid of this.
Oh, that guy's a real piece of work.
Can you talk to him?
You're so good at yellin' at people.
Fine, I'll take care of it.
Thanks, Red. You're a lifesaver.
I'll go call him right now.
[Fez murmurs] I'll be right in.
-Did you do have fun cutting off my balls?
-What?
I should be the one
dealing with the landlord.
I need Sherri to see
that I am invested in our relationship.
Fine, call the landlord.
Just get this tree outta my driveway.
Oh, Mr. Red!
[Fez gasps]
-What the hell?!
-[Fez yelps]
I don't know what you heard,
but… this show ain't free.
They eat my popsicles,
they take over my basement,
and they turn my life upside down.
Dumbasses!
Okay, now you're starting
to sound like your grandpa.
Let's not forget how much you love it here
and how you can't wait to come back.
Come back?
I… I just want to get out of this…
this crappy Podunk town.
Well, I have carved out
a pretty nice life here in Point Place.
But I guess that doesn't matter.
Hey. I know I'm early.
Mom. [gasps]
I tried to call,
but it sounded like someone was
banging the phone around in a pot.
Mom, thank God you're here.
Everything's ruined.
My boyfriend broke up with me,
and for some reason I took it out on Gwen.
-Boyfriend?
-Jay Kelso.
Kelso?
We talk all the time.
You don't mention any of this?
Well, no, I think…
I think what is truly important here
is that Leia had a hoot this summer.
Which she seems to be forgetting.
Movie nights,
trips to the lake house, the rave--
-A rave?
-Oh, don't be such a square, Donna.
Look, I'll explain everything in the car.
Right now I just need
to get out of this hellhole.
Well, would a hellhole have
such a catchy commercial?
♪ Everything points to this place ♪
-Let me… talk to her for a sec?
Fine.
[Kitty hesitates]
George Harrison's sister lived here.
Mom, I… [scoffs]
I feel so stupid.
I thought I was having
this perfect summer, and…
now it's all ruined.
Honey, breakups suck.
How would you know?
You've been with Dad since high school.
-Actually, we broke up a lot.
-You did?
Yeah, and one of those times
I dated Jay's uncle, Casey.
A Kelso?
Yeah.
Look, being a teenager gets messy.
Whenever I was going through something,
you know who helped me through it?
My friends.
So just go talk to Gwen.
What is it with these Kelsos?
-It's the hair.
-I know. It's so perfect.
-[both chuckling]
-[rock music playing]
Thanks again for helping me
deal with my landlord.
That was the sexiest thing
you've ever done.
I mean, besides the way
you say "pistachio."
Mmm…
-Pistachio.
-[Sherri moans]
I don't know what's happening,
but it seems weird.
Oh, Gwen. You remember my friend, Fez?
Yeah, your "friend" used all my bodywash.
It's so nice to meet
another fan of the cucumber-melon.
Can I have 20 bucks?
I need to get something for Leia.
Oh, allow me.
Oh yeah, I feel it.
[strains, chuckles]
Fifty it is.
Thanks, new Dad. [chuckles]
Oh, that was awful sweet of you.
Well, I'm a problem solver, baby.
[chuckles]
Oh. Good.
'Cause my landlord's here.
So…
Oh…
It's you.
-Fenton, what are you doing here?
-I own this place.
Along with three other homes,
one duplex, and a Dippin' Dots.
Yeah. Take it all in, Fez.
This is what success looks like.
Oh, I know what success looks like.
Have you heard of Chez Fez?
[scoffs] Barely.
I sat through one of your annoying
commercials when I was in the bath.
I'd already put in my salt, so I didn't
wanna get out and change the channel.
Which is a long way of saying
I have a TV in my bathroom, bitch.
Okay, then! Now that we're
all caught up on everything, I guess--
When you signed your lease,
it specifically said
no pets over 150 pounds.
I'm 149!
With those thighs?
-I'd rather these thighs than that face.
-I'd rather this face than those shoes.
-I'd rather these shoes than no hair.
-[gasps] Go to hell!
I'll see you there!
Let's not get our panties in a bunch.
We still gotta deal with that tree.
[chuckles] I'm not touching that tree
until you pay your rent.
-Which just went up because of that.
-What?
And stay the hell away from
my Dippin' Dots!
You will never taste
the ice cream of the future.
-Pistach--
-I am not in the mood!
[rock music playing]
Hi, Jay.
Mrs. Forman?
It's time we had a little chat.
How did you know I was here?
Oh, this is my town, sweetie.
I have eyes everywhere.
How's Leia doing?
I mean, I feel really bad about
how things went down, but I had to do it.
Well, that is what
I wanted to talk to you about.
She is so upset,
she may not come back next summer.
That's not what I wanted.
This isn't about you!
[forced laughter]
No, no, it is about you, honey.
You were saying?
I wasn't trying to hurt her, Mrs. Forman.
It's just, you know, anything can happen.
What if she meets someone else?
Or what if I get asked
to star in the next Karate Kid?
I mean, I'd have to move to Reseda!
Okay, okay.
Let me tell you a little story about
a long distance relationship of mine.
I was dating this boy
I was madly in love with.
And then the war started.
He was being shipped overseas.
World War I?
[sharp exhale]
Anyway, we decided
we would still give it a shot.
And I never regretted that decision.
And that guy was Red?
No, I think his name was Steve.
So your point is
long distance doesn't work?
Not with Steve.
He had a giant belly button.
I could see it through his sweaters.
The point is, at least we tried.
Honey, don't go through life
wondering what could have been.
You're squeezing my hand pretty hard,
Mrs. Forman. [chuckles]
I really want you to give it a try.
It's getting tighter.
I open a lot of mayonnaise jars.
[rock guitar riff playing]
Shh.
A fly landed on my crotch, and I'm trying
to decide if it's worth the swat.
-[fly buzzing]
-Damn. It flew away.
That's probably a good thing.
-Oh, where's Gwen?
-She's out somewhere.
I don't want to leave
without saying goodbye to her.
I totally overreacted.
This is my first breakup,
and I'm not handling it too well.
Yeah, it sucks.
My first breakup felt like my heart
was getting ripped out of my butt, so…
And it made it even worse
that everyone was agreeing with Jay.
Not everyone.
Look, I was in a tough spot
'cause Jay's my best friend, but
I agree with you.
-You do?
-Yeah.
And then Nikki chimed in
talking about living separate lives,
and… I got worried I'd get
my heart ripped out of my butt again.
Come on, Nate. That's just how she is.
I know. I just…
I wish she wasn't always so…
-God, there just isn't a word for it.
-Practical?
Cool. We just invented a word!
Well, thanks for telling me
all this, Nate.
It's nice to know there's
another hopeless romantic out there.
[chuckles] Yeah.
I mean, what's more powerful than love?
Maybe lightning. But that's it.
Right. If two people are meant to be,
then they can survive anything.
Exactly.
Do you know how lucky it is
to find that special person?
Someone who you feel comfortable with?
-And someone you can talk to.
-And everything's just easy.
-Right. I mean, someone who just…
-Gets you?
-Yeah.
What the hell?!
-Leia?!
-Gwen?!
-Nate?!
There was a fly on my junk.
[rock music playing]
[chill rock music playing]
Oh, that Fenton makes my blood boil.
But I also want to be there for Sherri.
Oh, so much drama. Right, mama?
Who are you?
I think he's banging Gwen's mom.
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Oh, and we had just rekindled
the flame to our relationship.
Then Fenton just stomped it out.
Oh, cry with me.
[sobbing]
Sorry. I can't get water from a stone.
Oh, you two are no help.
I miss my people.
[electric guitar riff plays]
Maybe this life doesn't even matter,
you know?
Maybe we're not even here.
Or, no. Maybe I'm here, but you're not.
[terrified gasp] Hello?
[laughing]
Oh!
Man.
I just totally forgot why I was laughing.
Isn't that funny? [coughs]
I'm losing my patience with you, man.
You gotta get with her.
I mean, there's nothing more beautiful
than when two people
fit together perfectly like…
Well, like two of these potato…
How do they do this?!
That's it?
I have to let go of my grudge with Fenton
to fix my relationship with Sherri.
Fez, what are you doing here?
Donna? Oh, this is so great.
The old gang is here.
Maybe we should get you some fresh air.
Donna, Donna. I can't.
Eric is my best friend.
[rock music playing]
-How?
-I don't know.
-Why?
-I do not know.
[groans] He's Jay's best friend.
He's Nikki's boyfriend.
He's your brother.
Ugh!
This is so bad.
[chuckles]
-Why are you laughing?
-Sorry.
I was just thinking about
the first time we came up here.
You'd never had a beer.
You'd never kissed anyone.
You never stopped
talking about debate club.
Oh…
I was such a dork.
But now look at you.
You're an agent of chaos. I love it.
Gwen, what do I do now?
There's nothing to do.
You didn't kiss Nate.
You don't owe Jay anything.
So, for now, you go back to Chicago,
you call me every freaking day,
we see each other as much as we can,
and then come back next summer,
and we do it all again.
I like this plan.
Hang on. I got you something.
Wanna break one more law before you go?
At this point, why the hell not?
[both laughing]
I don't know what you said to Fenton,
but he's completely backed off.
He's getting rid of that tree,
and he promised to re-carpet the bathroom.
[Fez chuckles]
Well, I like you,
so I put my ego aside
and, uh, made him a peace offering.
Well, I made that birch my bitch.
Guess I can take this off now.
Take a picture. It'll last longer.
[Fez imitates shutter clicking]
-[laughs]
-[door shuts]
[Fez sighs contentedly]
I got that hair
from a dog groomer. [chuckles]
I win.
Hey, thanks for helping me out
with this, Fez.
Most guys would have just
left me in the lurch.
Oh, hearing you say that
makes me emotional.
And those emotions
are going into my pants.
Oh, my body's such a puzzle.
Well, let's go into the bedroom
and put our pieces together.
Oh, I was hoping to have sex, but…
Sure, whatever.
Let's do what you wanna do.
[rock music playing]
-Thanks for everything, Grandpa.
-Come here, kiddo.
Loved having you around.
You.
But you tell your friends,
the basement is off-limits
while you're gone.
My turn! My turn!
Oh!
I love you, honey.
[cooing] Tell your friends
they can use the basement
as much as they want while you're gone.
Thanks, Grandma. I love you too.
-[laughs happily]
-[Leia] Okay!
Grandpa, it's getting tighter!
Kitty!
She's tappin' out.
Hey.
We don't have to talk about it.
It was nothing.
Right.
Really?
-No, it was something.
-Yeah, it was definitely something.
Leia!
I'm so glad I caught you before you left.
-Oh. Hey, bro.
-Nothing.
What are you doing here?
I did some soul-searching
and a crap ton of karate,
and I realized I was wrong.
I'm not ready to give up on us.
And… I know I was a jerk,
but if you give me another chance, Leia,
I will spend every day
making it up to you.
Jay, that's…
That's so sweet, I…
I'm just a little confused right now.
Maybe this will help.
That was a good one.
Um, Gwen?
She'll call you when she gets to Chicago.
-Not if I call you first.
-Okay, keep it moving.
Okay, Le-Le. Last goodbyes, we gotta go.
-You're calling me soon as you get home.
-Oh, we have a lot to talk about.
Smile!
[shutter clicks]
That was the last picture. My job is done.
I am so sorry.
-What?
-Nothing.
Get in the car. Get in the car.
I'm really gonna miss her.
-[car engine starts]
-[Nate sighs]
Me too.
[snickers] Not.
Leia, nooo!
It's okay, buddy.
-[sobbing]
-["Kids in America" by The Muffs playing]
Come back, Leia! Come baaack!
♪ Looking out a dirty old window ♪
♪ Outside the cars in the city
Go rushing by ♪
♪ I sit here alone and I wonder why ♪
♪ Friday night and everyone's moving ♪
♪ I can feel the heat
But it's soothing, heading down ♪
♪ I search for the beat
In this dirty town ♪
♪ Downtown the young ones are going ♪
♪ Downtown the young ones are growing ♪
-♪ We're the kids in America ♪
-♪ Whoa-oh ♪
♪ Everybody live for the music-go-round ♪
♪ Bright lights, the music gets faster ♪
♪ Look, boy, don't check on your watch
Not another glance ♪
♪ I'm not leaving now, honey
Not a chance ♪
♪ Hotshot, give me no problems ♪
♪ Much later, baby
You'll be saying never mind ♪
♪ You know life is cruel
Life is never kind ♪
♪ Kind hearts don't make a new story ♪
♪ Kind hearts don't grab any glory ♪
-♪ We're the kids in America ♪
-♪ Whoa-oh ♪
♪ Everybody live for the music-go-round ♪