[rock guitar riff playing]
[Leia, hoarsely] Cookie.
Could we please stop the 90210 marathon?
I had a dirty dream
about Andrea Zuckerman.
I'm so confused.
This show is the only thing
getting me through my breakup with Jay.
Oh, I know you're hurting.
But, again, you actually have to date
someone to break up with them.
[Leia scoffs] I like it better under here.
Oh my God. Still with the 90210?
This is getting pathetic.
I'm not gonna say it to her face,
but she needs professional help.
I saw her yesterday wandering
just through the neighborhood
like our grandpa used to.
Near the end.
Guys, stop.
She's going through something.
Something really stupid.
Gwen! I'm right here!
Good. You needed to hear it.
[scoffs]
How long am I going to feel this bad?
It takes about half the time
you were in a relationship to get over it.
And since you were never
in a relationship…
You're good.
[Leia scoffs]
Leia, come on.
Don't go back into your sad hole.
We came by to give you
your birthday present.
[chill psychedelic music playing]
Guys, I love it. How did you know my size?
We got you an extra large
so we can enjoy it too.
Is this chair too small?
Just give Leia our birthday card already.
Inside cat.
[gasps] Outside cat.
Inside cat. Outside cat. Ins--
No more cat.
I missed you guys.
My sad hole was lonely without you.
I'm not gonna let my breakup with Jay
ruin my birthday.
Not a breakup.
[both] Not a breakup.
How many times
do you turn 15 in your life?
Not that many.
I'm over him.
New year, new me.
New Kids On The Block.
I over-corrected.
What's this?
You spelled my name wrong on this card.
How do you not know
how to spell your girlfriend's name?
Let me see that.
-[Nikki scoffs]
-[chuckles]
Nik!
People are leaving? I just got this right.
-[rock music playing]
-One, two, three, four!
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
♪ We're all all right! ♪
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
Well, Donna and Eric aren't gonna make it
for Leia's birthday.
Eric's upset, but he knew the risks
when he signed up for Space Camp.
Kitty, he fell out of his bunk bed.
It's not exactly Apollo 13.
Well, he is gonna wish
he slept on the bottom bunk
because I am throwing
a classic Kitty Forman birthday bash.
It's you and me, old friend.
We're about to put on a show.
You're planning a kid's party.
So let's try and not
get all stressed out this time.
Don't worry.
I woke up early to get a head start.
Oh my God, it's 7:00 a.m.
I haven't deviled a damn thing!
Well, I did my part.
Took care of the gift.
Twenty dollars.
-You did one thing. Good for you.
-[egg cracks]
I'm sorry. I snapped.
It's… Birthdays are fun.
[laughs]
It's gonna be a long day.
Hey there! Hi there! Ho there!
And it just got longer.
-Bob. You made it.
-[Bob laughs]
[Kitty coos]
You knew about this?
And you didn't, and that's why he's here.
-Hi!
-[Bob] Hi.
I brought you some fresh Florida oranges.
I used them as a pillow on the plane.
So, if you find any curly hairs in there,
that's me.
Well, I am just gonna put these
in the dishwasher.
[both laugh]
There's the birthday girl!
Happy birthday.
I said it first.
Hey, Grandpa Bob.
Ooh! Look at you.
You are so darn beautiful.
Those Pinciotti genes
are strong like a bull.
Bull-something.
That milk's for the party!
I mean, happy birthday, honey.
Happy birthday, kiddo.
Is Grandma all right?
I'd lay low.
[rock music playing]
If you don't even know
how I spell my name,
what else do you not know about me?
I don't know what I don't know, Nik.
Ask me something about your boobs.
I can draw those on a napkin.
You're buying us lunch on your birthday?
I felt like I needed to thank you guys
for taking care of me this week.
I wasn't too bad, was I?
[laughs heartily, inhales sharply]
Oh, you weren't kidding.
I'm glad you finally realized it's dumb
to let a man waste so much of your time.
That's our job.
You're right.
I'm going to have a great birthday.
All that moping around stuff
is in the past.
Good.
'Cause Jay and Serena just walked in.
This is bad. She's gonna have a relapse.
Yeah. Leia, you don't need this right now.
Let's just get outta here.
Seriously, guys, I'm fine.
I'm gonna go over there
and say hi like a normal person.
How's it going, turkeys?
I like her body language.
Strong, assertive.
She just picked up a pickle.
So today's my birthday. [chuckles]
New year, startin' fresh.
The big one-five.
Aww, that's so cute!
I barely even remember turning 15.
I think I was in the Bahamas.
Me too!
But you're here right now.
No, you're here.
Anywhistle, big party tonight.
My grandma's inviting her bridge club,
so the roof shall be raised.
[chuckles]
Actually, I'm so rude.
You guys should come.
-Are you sure?
-Of course.
I want all my friends
and their new girlfriends at my party.
Okay, great. We'll be there.
As will I. Cannot wait.
[sighs] I just ruined my birthday.
This is where you're supposed to tell me
I didn't just ruin my birthday.
But you did.
This pickle's bad luck!
Don't put your demon pickle near me.
You wanna lose that hand?
You know, it's hard
to take the joy out of a cupcake.
But you did.
Well, if you don't wanna help me,
you can go sit in the living room
and talk to Bob
about his prosthetic testicle.
Why did you have to invite him?
I don't know what you're getting
worked up about. He's Leia's grandpa too.
I blame Eric.
There's only one girl in the world
with Bob as her dad,
and he had to pick her.
Hey there, what's cookin'?
-'Cause we're in the kitchen.
-Oh.
Damn it.
We said his name three times
and summoned him like Beetlejuice.
I'm gonna make my famous clam dip
for the party.
Oh, that's sweet,
but we have plenty of food for tonight.
I know, but the kids are gonna want
something good.
I was thawing a ham in there.
I'm just excited.
You know, I went all out
on Leia's birthday gift this year.
I got her a karaoke machine.
-Aren't those things expensive?
-Oh yeah. [chuckles]
I left the price tag on.
'Cause I want her to…
[voice breaking]
…remember how much I love her.
[weeping] I need a minute!
This guy thinks he can run my party?
Clam my ham? No, sir!
You can rinse off your ham, Kitty.
My 20 bucks is getting its ass kicked
by a karaoke machine.
Well, then, step it up, Red.
You've got twice the balls, act like it.
[rock music playing]
You guys, I think I figured out
why I invited Jay and his girlfriend
to my party.
You ready?
I'm not over Jay.
-Oh my God. No way.
-What?
[chuckles] I know!
I'm surprised too.
And it's all my fault.
Because, guys…
-I'm Brenda.
-Brenda?
-Brenda Walsh, from 90210.
-[Ozzie sighs]
Brenda obsesses over the guy,
but she never goes for the guy.
[pop rock theme music playing]
[percussion plays]
[class bell ringing]
All my life, people told me
I was running away.
But, really,
I've been running to something.
It's me, isn't it?
It is.
Hey, Leia. I'm DJing a party tonight.
You wanna come? It's gonna be fresh.
Not now, David.
It's because I'm a freshman, isn't it?
[pop rock theme music plays]
So Brenda's the passive,
overly dramatic doormat.
This makes sense now.
[gasps and laughs] I know, right?
But you know who always gets the guy?
Kelly, the popular blonde
with the rich-girl attitude.
[pop rock theme music playing]
[percussion plays]
[upbeat rock music playing]
All my life, people told me
I was running away.
But, really,
I've been running to something.
It's me, isn't it?
No, bitch. It's me.
-Leia?
-It's Kelly.
Hey, guys. I'm DJing a party tonight.
You wanna come? It's gonna be fresh.
Not now, David.
It's because I'm a freshman, isn't it?
[pop rock theme plays, fades out]
I like it.
Mind if I riff on it a little bit?
[pop rock theme music playing]
[percussion plays]
Hey, guys. I'm DJing a party.
It's gonna be fresh.
This totally rad breakdancer's
gonna be there. Check it.
Drop that beat.
[old school hip-hop beat playing]
[students exclaiming]
That's the coolest kid I've ever seen!
[pop rock theme music plays, fades out]
Really, dude?
David don't lie.
When Jay and Serena show up at my party,
I'm gonna show 'em what's what.
Kelly-style.
This is why we get paid 30% less than men.
What happened to not obsessing over Jay?
I'm not obsessing.
I'm just gonna change how I look
and how I act and how I think
to win him back.
-Hey! What was that for?
-To snap you out of it.
Dude!
Hey!
Ow. Stop.
I am the wrong audience for this.
[Leia] Ow!
-I got the gift.
-[Kitty gasps]
-Where's Bob?
-Oh.
Well…
He was driving me crazy, so I…
I put some cold medicine in his iced tea.
And some in his potato salad.
Some more in his pudding.
He just… He wouldn't go down, Red.
It was like… drugging a rhino.
Anyhoo, he's fast asleep upstairs.
Wait till you see what I got Leia.
Bob went expensive, but I went thoughtful.
You sweet, sweet man.
Her own cordless drill.
You stupid, stupid man.
But it's a great gift.
It gives her independence.
She can fix things on her own.
Take care of herself.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Did I not say it was cordless?
Red, you need to think like a teenager.
What did you want when you were 15?
A vaccine for polio.
All right. I'll keep looking.
Man… I must have been really tired.
I fell asleep in the hallway.
Well… you know,
that jet lag can be a killer.
Let me get you some more iced tea.
[rock music playing]
[Kitty] Ooh!
Somebody brought their appetite.
So which one of my hors d'oeuvres
do you like best?
This clam dip? Love!
Whoopsie.
Okay, I've figured out high heels.
You can let go now.
So you're gonna stand here
and wait for Jay?
Yeah. And when he gets here,
I'm gonna grab him and Kelly his face off.
[dramatic rock guitar riff plays]
This is so embarrassing.
I thought I could win back Jay,
but he didn't even care enough to show.
I get it.
No one came to watch me
DJ at the Peach Pit.
Not even Donna Martin.
It's the worst.
What was she like? I mean, between scenes?
What do you mean, "scenes"?
Never mind.
Thank you for coming
to my birthday, David.
-You were always my favorite.
-I'll take it.
Who are you talking to?
Uh, David. Nobody.
This is stupid.
I wasted my whole birthday
thinking about Jay,
and he's clearly moved on.
I'm done being pathetic.
Finally!
-[doorbell chimes]
-Move, he's here! Move, he's here!
Grandpa Bob?
You mean Grandpa Tom Jones.
I'm here to sing your birthday song
on your birthday gift.
You're gonna sing?
In front of my friends? In that jacket?
I'll be over here.
Tom Jones?
More like Tom groans
getting up from the couch. Am I right?
I am right.
[soft karaoke instrumental playing]
Wrong song, but, hey, the show must go on.
I'd like to dedicate this song
to my beautiful granddaughter, Leia.
This one's for you.
Oh no.
♪ Close your eyes ♪
♪ Make a wish ♪
♪ And blow out the candlelight ♪
Hey, it worked out. It's a birthday song.
This is not a birthday song.
We'll ride it out together.
♪ I'll make love to you ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ And I'll hold you tight ♪
♪ Baby, all through the night… ♪
This is our song. [chuckles]
[Bob continues singing]
It was playing on the radio the first time
you let me touch your butt.
Oh, you remembered!
♪ And I will not let go
Till you tell me to ♪
Wanna get some air?
Oh God, yes.
♪ Girl, relax ♪
Bob. Nobody's relaxed.
Seems like you might have had
a rough night, kiddo.
I've only been 15 for a day,
and so far I don't like it.
I mean, nothing's gone right.
It's like I don't know what I'm doing.
Well,
everything's not gonna go right.
Give yourself a break.
You're half dumbass.
It's just…
Everyone else seems to have it all
figured out and I'm just making it all up.
Well, I hate to break it to you, kid,
but we're all just making it up
as we go along.
So don't be so hard on yourself.
Thanks, Grandpa.
Oh. Hey, wait.
Don't you want your present?
["Slow Ride" opening riff playing]
♪ Slow ride… ♪
A car? You got me a car?
It belonged to your father.
Tomorrow, we'll get your learner's permit,
and I'll teach you how to drive. Okay?
Thank you, Grandpa.
This is the best present I've ever gotten.
Oh…
Be sure to say that to Grandpa Bob.
Happy birthday, kiddo.
-♪ Slow ridin' woman, you're so fine ♪
-[song fades out]
You gave her the Vista Cruiser?
Man, you really creamed my jeans.
Can't you even lose like a normal person?
Now, Red, it wasn't a competition.
I wanted to do something nice for Leia.
You guys are lucky
to spend all this time with her.
I don't want her
to forget about her ol' Grandpa Bob.
Oh.
Damn it.
You're a good man, Bob.
Annoying as hell, but a good man.
Leia is lucky to have you.
You guys are makin' me emotional.
And I never cry.
Bob, you are welcome here anytime.
[chuckles]
Ooh.
I gotta see a man about a clam. [chuckles]
"Anytime"?
Red, he's family.
[grumbles] Eric!
[rapping on window]
Jay?
Hey. Mind if I come in?
Okay, but the party's over.
[strains] Yeah. I'm sorry I missed it.
It just didn't feel right
to show up with Serena.
I still don't know why I invited her.
-I just wanted you to be there.
-I wanted to be there too.
But… at least I can wish you
a happy birthday.
You know? Before it's too late.
Whoa. Where did that come from?
I guess I'm just
making it up as I go along.
-You need to break up with Serena.
-Serena who?
[Jay chuckles]
["The World I Know"
by Collective Soul playing]
Hey, you wanna go for a drive?
Yeah, but I don't have a car.
[laughs softly] Not a problem.
♪ So I walk up on high… ♪
-Hey, we kissed.
-I know.
This is the best birthday.
[siren wails]
Just be cool.
You mean, for the first time in my life?!
♪ While the tears roll down ♪
♪ 'Cause it's the world I know ♪
♪ Oh, it's the world I know ♪
[rock music playing]