So… how was last night?
Did you break up with your boyfriend?
Aren't you just dying to know?
Oh, I'm on pins and needles.
Well, he took me
to one of those fancy places
where you order at the table.
Wow!
He spoils you.
Well, he can afford it.
I don't know if I mentioned this,
but he's kind of a local celebrity.
Is it Gary Storm?
The weather guy on Channel 2 news?
I love his bow ties.
Gary Storm died in a tornado.
You're thinking of Johnny Thunder.
Oh my God! You're dating Johnny Thunder?
No, no. My guy's not a weatherman.
He's got a bunch of salons.
You may have seen his commercials.
Where's the hair?
There's the hair.
Explosion.
Chez Fez, where every day
is a good hair day.
I said, good day.
You're dating Fez?
You know Fez?
Oh, we know Fez.
-One, two, three, four!
Hello, Wisconsin!
Do they know you guys are here?
Oh, they don't care.
They're in the zone.
Nothing breaks it.
Watch this.
How can she kiss my brother?
His dentist quit in the middle of an exam.
Guys.
I got too close, and now I'm stuck in it.
We've all been there.
When you're in the middle of
a make out session,
and you're in the moment.
And your lips just melt together.
And his tongue hits the hangy thing
in the back of your throat
and it feels so good.
What?
The… uvula.
The U-spot?
Leia, have you ever kissed anyone?
Never. Not once.
It's just never happened, okay?
In sixth grade, I was a foot taller
than all the other boys.
And just when they got up to mouth level,
I did two years of advanced braces.
Like headgear?
It was so much worse.
There was a crank
my parents had to tighten every night.
It was like starting an old-timey car.
Well, it was worth it.
You have such a beautiful smile.
Do you ever take a day off?
I wanna kiss someone.
I think about it all the time.
What's it like?
Okay. This is an emergency.
We need to get you your first kiss.
Let's go to the mall and knock this out.
The mall?
Oh, don't make me start on a mannequin.
That's so embarrassing!
No. It's full of guys.
We'll find some goober, chat him up,
show him your teeth, lay one on him.
I don't want my first kiss
to be with a goober.
You're right.
We should just wait until
you're confident enough,
emotionally ready, secure in who you are--
Okay, okay! Mall.
Summer of our first kiss. Right, Ozzie?
Don't lump me in with you,
you mouth virgin.
I have Etienne.
Bro, I wanna support you, but you gotta
stop with the fake Canadian boyfriend.
Oh, he's real as hell.
My parents took me
to see Phantom of the Opera in Montreal.
And I met the cutest guy… Etienne.
We were both reaching for
the last kids' XL souvenir sweatshirt.
And he let me keep it.
We've never seen the sweatshirt.
Whatever. You wouldn't know romance
if it threw acid in your face,
forcing you into a life of solitude,
composing the music of the night.
God, I hope he's real.
When did you guys get here?
We were making out.
Fez was one of Eric's friends.
He started out
as a foreign exchange student, but…
then I guess someone forgot
to exchange him back.
Where is he from?
I hear it's just lovely there.
So, what did he say when you told him
you didn't wanna see him anymore?
I didn't get that far.
I mean, I tried.
I told him it was over, and he said…
Over, under. I don't care.
I'm flexible, baby.
So I said,
"I'm trying to focus on myself."
I understand!
And I'd like to watch you.
Watch you focus on yourself.
And then I said, "We gotta
act like adults here. We gotta talk."
I can't.
My mouth is full.
He sucked off two of my Lee Press Ons.
Well…
He's got a strong tongue. That's fine.
No. He really is a lovely guy,
and he obviously likes you.
Maybe see where it goes.
Kitty, I really took
all that advice you gave me to heart.
I need to stop jumping from guy to guy
and focus on myself for a while.
Darn it. That was good advice.
I don't know what to do.
Normally, when I break up with a guy,
I just tell the parole officer
to check his pee,
and it takes care of itself, you know?
Why don't I go talk to him?
Maybe I can let him down easy.
Oh good. 'Cause if I do it,
I'm definitely gonna sleep with him again.
What? I was trying to focus on myself,
and last night myself wanted
to have sex with that guy, so…
Welcome back to Chez Fez.
It's always an honor
to have your hair in my chair.
Well, I love coming here.
I'm always so happy
to see how well you're doing.
I mean, free Tootsie Rolls.
Are you made of money?
Yes. Can you believe it?
I tell you, Ms. Kitty. I love my life.
My business is booming.
I have the waist of Linda Evangelista.
And, as you know,
I have taken a lover.
Actually,
I wanted to talk to you about Sherri.
Oh yeah. She's so beautiful, right?
She's warm and gooey,
like a chicken pot pie.
Uh-huh.
-But--
-Oh, and don't get me started on her butt.
It's like the eighth
and ninth Wonder of the World.
Ms. Kitty, I haven't felt this way
about a woman since, uh…
-Jackie.
Yes!
Whatever happened between you two?
Oh, Ms. Kitty!
We were at Hedonism Resort.
In Hamaica.
And I caught her on the phone one night…
…with Michael.
Kelso?
Dukakis.
Yes, of course Kelso!
She left me there.
And I spent the next five days
getting kicked out of hot tubs
for talking too much.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
Oh, but that is the past.
And Sherri is my future.
You know, Ms. Kitty,
when I'm with her… I'm no longer a man.
I'm like a little boy
seeing the world for the first time.
Don't get me wrong, I still have
the voice of a man and the… hips of a man
and, uh… the mouth of a man.
It's very confusing.
But when I hold her in my arms…
Oh, Ms. Kitty.
It's like the world just melts away…
and there's only us,
for eternity.
I'm sorry, Ms. Kitty.
What were you saying?
I was saying…
-I love love!
-Oh!
Don't ever let her go!
Thanks for the ride, Grandpa.
Any time you kids wanna
get out of my house, I'll drive you.
This shouldn't take too long.
You guys need anything?
A miracle.
Fine.
I'll be right over here, reading my paper.
You have great taste.
This is the new ionic massage chair.
-Let me show you some of the features.
-Look. I know you're just doing your job.
But go do it over there.
Any place that's not here.
You are gonna have to do
better than that to get rid of me.
It's got variable speeds,
Corinthian leather,
and if you turn that frown upside-down,
I'll throw in same-day delivery.
I'm about to same-day deliver
your ass into that planter if you…
Oh…
Sweet Lord.
This chair's got fingers!
All I need is, like, a credit card.
Just make it happen.
I'm really nervous.
My back sweat's
being funneled right into my butt.
That's just your body
getting ready for romance.
You're cute, you're smart,
and you're awesome. You can do this.
It's a total sausage fest.
Yeah, look at all these guys.
No. Hickory Farms is giving out
free samples.
Etienne loves a nice smoked Gouda.
-Fine. If he's real, what's his last name?
-St. Bernard.
-What school?
-St. Bernard's.
-Does he have any pets?
-Bichon Frisé.
Wait. That reminds me.
I've given CPR to a dog.
Does that count as a kiss?
-Go. You got this!
I'd like two scoops. Of you.
I'm sorry.
Hey, sexy. You eatin' grapes?
Yeah, because he's nine.
I'm so sorry. My dad has that shirt!
Ma'am, you are not allowed
behind the counter.
I don't care anymore.
Now put down the scooper,
and let's do this.
You don't have to make this so difficult!
Got away.
-Okay!
-You kids need to leave.
You don't happen
to have a son my age, do you?
So it went well?
No. Let's go. Where's Gwen?
Gwen, let's bounce.
Gwen!
Bye, Kevin. That was fun.
Best day of my life.
Calm down, Kevin.
Okay.
Seriously?
One of us had to get some.
Babe, I think you might be having
a reaction to one of my Lip Smackers.
Really?
I feel fine.
Yeah, it looks fine.
That was a disaster.
And I'm on a list now, so I can't go back.
-What if I need new shoes?
-What do you mean, "what if"?
Whoa, gross.
Why does your mouth
look like a monkey's ass?
A monkey's ass?
Like, in a good or bad way?
Come on. We should probably
get you to the urgent care.
You said it wasn't bad.
I was just comfortable,
and I didn't wanna get up.
Oh my God. I'm at the mall
throwing myself at randos.
Meanwhile, they're making out so much,
his lips revolted.
What's wrong with me?
Doesn't anyone want
to lick these $2,000 teeth?
Wow. Okay.
Well, there is another idea,
but I didn't wanna bring it up
because it feels
kinda weird and desperate.
I think we're there.
You could kiss Jay.
He's cute. He's always flirting with you.
Plus, he's a Kelso.
So? What does that mean?
He's a man-whore.
Oh.
As great as that sounds, I'm gonna pass.
Plus, he's our friend. It's too awkward.
There's gotta be someone else.
There's always Town Pool Ricky.
Oh great, a lifeguard. That's hot.
No, he just hangs out
and collects the floating Band-Aids.
But he's single and ready to mingle.
At least that's what his shirt says.
So Jay?
Jay, it is.
Red, I'm not sure
about this massage chair.
We said we wouldn't change anything
in case one of us went blind.
I'm sorry, gorgeous.
The last thing I wanna do
is stress you out or upset you.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm awesome.
Kitty, you did a terrible job with Fez.
He told me he loved me.
What did you say to him?
I… I'm an older lady.
I can't recall the exact words.
Kitty. He talked about a life together.
He started crying.
Then he got his mom on the phone.
She started crying.
Honey.
Sherri's here.
I know she is. I'm not sure you are.
Good one, babe.
I'm sorry. I just… I got…
I got swept up in the moment.
He's so sweet.
And his words sound like
a romance novel that I barely understand.
What am I gonna do?
This guy is undumpable.
Well, clearly, I can't hack it.
We need someone who is just ruthless.
Who will go straight for the jugular.
An ax murderer.
Red, honey?
Should we get a cat?
Just something warm to have right here,
while I'm… chillin'.
Chair, I need to talk to the real Red.
Damn it, Kitty!
Did you have to pull the plug?
That's exactly why I don't put your name
on those papers at the hospital.
There's our ax murderer.
Hey, you.
Where is everyone? I thought
we're meeting up here before bowling.
Oh, the bowling alley's closed.
They ran out of balls.
Come sit.
Okay.
Look at that sky.
The stars are so bright, and the moon is
also bright.
I never thought of it like that.
Kind of romantic, don't you think?
Whoa, you can see
right into that old lady's bathtub.
Oh, she's crying.
I think her husband just died.
-Leia?
-Yeah?
I know what's going on here.
Oh good. Gimme a sec.
Okay, I'm back.
Leia.
I'm not going to kiss you.
What?
Not even you?
Oh my God, this is so embarrassing.
I'll be in here now.
Hey, stop. Don't be embarrassed.
Look. I think you're great.
You're cute and smart and interesting.
Really?
Yeah.
That's why I don't think we should kiss.
Look.
Leia, I just don't want to be
some meaningless hookup.
You know?
Like, if it's gonna happen,
I want it to just happen.
And I want it to be amazing.
Okay, that was really nice.
You sure you don't wanna kiss?
Because my back sweat is
really telling me it's time for romance.
Let's just see where the summer takes us.
Who knows?
It might be somewhere really special.
Hello, Mr. Red.
Oh.
Fez, you're here. Good.
Look.
There's no easy way to say this.
It's over.
Oh no.
That's terrible.
How long do you have left?
-What?
-Don't worry, Mr. Red.
I'll take care of Ms. Kitty
when you're gone.
In every possible way.
I'm talking about you and Sherri.
The two of you are over.
What?
What are you talking about?
Is this a joke?
-Knock, knock.
-Who's there?
Sherri's dumping you.
That's not funny.
Chin up, kid.
You gave it your best shot.
Look at me!
Look me in the eyes
if you're going to rip my heart out!
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Red.
I shouldn't have raised my voice.
But I saw a life for us.
Holidays, travel, dying of an old age
while making love so we could be
buried together like a pretzel.
Tough break.
Yeah. Really tough.
Everything else in my life
has lined up perfectly.
But the most important part,
someone to share it with…
it's missing.
Here's the thing, kid.
You're weird.
But, one day, you're gonna find
someone who loves that.
Besides, were you really ready for
the responsibility of a woman with kids?
She has kids?
It shouldn't be shocking
that a woman in her forties has kids.
She's in her forties?!
Whew!
Really dodged a bullet there.
I still can't believe Jay didn't kiss you.
It's so weird. Even though things didn't
turn out like I wanted, I'm not worried.
Kind of excited for what's next, you know?
I so do.
I just feel like a brand-new woman.
I can't wait to see
what's on the horizon for me--
Mom. Thanks for the ride, but could you
go get your groove back somewhere else?
Okay, okay. I'll go find myself
at Contempo Casual.
So what's the plan?
Just wait around for Jay?
If he wanted me to wait for around him,
he shouldn't have told me
how cute and smart and interesting I am.
You dork.
I've been telling you all along
how awesome you are,
but it took some guy to say it
for it all to sink in.
No.
Yeah, that's what happened.
Whatever. I like the new confident Leia.
Me too.
Actually, I'll be right back.
Bonjour, Etienne.
I miss you too.
What do you mean
your friends don't think I'm real?
It's the same thing
with these gauche Americans.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Yes.
Yes.